zyxware.com 2008-12-18

# Our Privacy Policy | Zyxware Technologies

Privacy Policy for Zyxware.com

The privacy of our visitors to Zyxware.com is important to us. 

At Zyxware.com, we recognize that privacy of your personal information is important. Here is information on what types of personal information we receive and collect when you use visit Zyxware.com, and how we safeguard your information. We never sell your personal information to third parties.

Log Files  
As with most other websites, we collect and use the data contained in log files. The information in the log files include your IP (internet protocol) address, your ISP (internet service provider, such as AOL or Shaw Cable), the browser you used to visit our site (such as Internet Explorer or Firefox), the time you visited our site and which pages you visited throughout our site. 

Cookies and Web Beacons  
We do use cookies to store information, such as your personal preferences when you visit our site. This could include only showing you a captcha once in your visit, or the ability to login to some of our features, such as forums.

We also use third party advertisements on Zyxwarecom to support our site. Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers information including your IP address, your ISP , the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed. This is generally used for geotargeting purposes or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited.

You can chose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in programs such as Norton Internet Security. However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites. This could include the inability to login to services or programs, such as logging into forums or accounts.

Bookmark/Search this post with:
